So the skeleton is in place, the logo is in place, but we need more.
So we've got our little table structure.
But what we need, Joshua, is what we need.
Our images we need we need the cakes.
I mean, that's not I it's got a very cool logo, the best cakes.
But we need the, um, the cakes, we need the images.
Now, obviously there's a real side.
And you selling cakes or doing something like that.
I'm going to suggest you take photos of your cakes.
But, uh, in the interest of not having time to bake nine different cakes, we are going to show you
a very sneaky trick.
Now, you don't want to just go on to.
You can go on to Images.google.com and search for cakes.
But now you've got to be careful.
There's copyrighted stuff out there and yeah, yeah, yeah.
So do find some really cool images and you can use this for all sorts of images.
You can go to Pixabay.com.
And here you can get royalty free images.
It's just beautiful.
You can drop them in.
They are shared by our generous community, 1 in 1 point 1 million images.
So it's super fantastic.
And there's so many cool images here.
So let's go.
What are we going to search for?
Uh, cakes.
Cakes cakes, cakes.
That's cakes is good.
Same as searching Google images.
What you can do is there is a specification here.
You can choose that you just want photos etc. you can even choose that you want transparent backgrounds.
And you can even start to say, well, you want it a certain sort of size.
So there it is.
And here we've got lots of cakes.
So what we're going to need to do is pick some delicious looking cakes.
So just tell me when you see a cake.
Yeah.
So let's just go from the top of this one okay.
Beautiful.
So again, all you got to do is, uh, open a new tabs because you're going to have quite a few.
Okay.
So we're going to open a couple of cakes in different tabs so that we can just quickly we're going to
ultimately need nine cakes, but we'll just show you us doing 1 or 2 just so you get the idea.
And uh, you can figure out the rest.
Um, delicious cakes.
So we'll just do one row.
Okay.
So here's one row of cakes.
So we're going to have that one that one.
And man this is looking good okay.
So what we would now need to do is what are we going to do.
We're going to have to download it.
We are going to have to download uh the.
So again there are um two ways we could do this.
We could link directly to this image copy image address.
Or as we showed you earlier you could download it.
Um, the problem with just linking directly to the image that is stored online in someone else's site,
if they delete it, you're going to have a problem on your website.
Um, downloading it means that you've got control over it, but it also means that if you want to publish
your website, you're going to have to put that image on line somewhere.
So let us download these images.
So we're just going to save them.
You can either choose save as or even better is if you choose free download you can actually choose
the size.
What should we go?
Should we just go with smallish images?
Maybe medium?
Yeah.
Well, I mean we the bottom line is we're not going to, uh, need really big images because we're just
going to stick them.
I mean, you can it's up to you.
Whatever you want to do with the images.
Um, okay.
And hit download and it's going to download that image.
So we're going to uh, I'm going to give them some sort of uh, sensible names.
Okay.
Uh, obviously you would give them a more intelligent name than that.
And then we're going to do the same for all our cakes.
So.
Okay.
So we're gonna download cake two.
And call that cake two and you're getting the idea about the stage and its download cake number three
at that resolution.
And so you would need to do this for all of your cakes, or you would have to have your own images.
But Pixabay is a really cool place to get yourself some images.
So there we have it.
We have now got three images downloaded and we're going to need to put them into our table.
So Josh what do you reckon.
It's got to be pretty simple.
Yeah.
So we've got all of our images there.
You can see decent size.
Delicious delicious.
Now again be careful with the size of your images.
This is a decent size.
It's a sort of midway size for the web.
You don't want it to be too high res because then it's going to be slower to to load.
But obviously you also want it to look vaguely decent on a on a nice retina display type image.
Uh, laptop or computer.
Okay, so now we can copy this.
Let's make sure we get the JPEG.
JPEG.
So now we copy this.
Come on.
See okay now we put our image in our table.
So I'm g.
Uh now it's we put our little link there.
So now it's got k three dot J peg.
Save this to see how our website is looking so far.
It's very big.
So it's our big mother cake.
You really get a you really get to see the detail on that.
Um, okay.
We can fiddle with the size of that just now, but let's put in our cakes, we'll first put in our thing,
then we can change the width.
Okay.
So we go back to finder.
Um, so actually we know the names.
We can just go like this.
Uh, hold down command.
And you see, there's going to be two cursors flashing like that.
So now when we go OMG they do everything at the same time.
See like that.
Now we can go.
Okay.
Um.
We don't even have to.
We just come on.
And we just got to change that to four.
Okay, we got one, two and three.
Yeah, two and one.
Okay, we're going backwards.
Yeah, whatever.
Anyhow, um, now we say that this is gonna look very stuffed, but we can change that now.
Right.
So as you can see, we do have our three cakes.
They are sitting in one row, in one table, but they are unique among us.
Okay.
So now using our little tip command.
Come on, come on.
Hold down command while you're clicking.
Now we can go.
We can change the width.
Um, equals.
What should we make it?
Oh, it sort of make it.
Uh, let's try 200 202 six.
Oh, no, no, 200, 200, 200, 200, 200, 201.
Okay, 201.
Save that.
it's cool.
Just experiment.
Yeah.
I think you went a bit bigger.
Okay.
307 300, 707, 300.
He never listens to me.
That's his problem.
Oh, I listen to you the first time.
Okay.
Not bad, not bad.
Not bad.
All right, so there.
We've got a row.
We've got a row of three little cakes.
Uh, not looking too bad.
And, uh.
Yeah.
So what we're going to have to now do is we're not going to make you suffer it.
We'd probably want to put in a few more rows of cake so we can have it look a little bit better.
But there we have it so far.
Uh, over to you to get that set up on your side to see if you can get your page with a little logo
and a row of cakes in it, or 2 or 3.
And I think we're getting close to having something happen here.
So remember the the whole plan, the whole plan is to end up with something like that.
Um, and we will fiddle with it some more in the next lesson.
And so people can look at those, click on something and see a recipe.